Deliver my command.
نفذ أمري.
I will enter seclusion for one month.
سأدخل في عزلة لمدة شهر.
When I emerge,
عندما اخرج،
I will wipe out the righteous sects, leaving no survivors.
سأقضي على الطوائف الصالحة، ولن أترك أي ناجين.
Those who obey shall prosper, those who defy shall perish.
من يطيعون ينجحون، ومن يخالفون يهلكون.
As you command.
كما تأمر.
May the Cult Leader rule for eternity and unite the three realms.
ليحكم زعيم الطائفة إلى الأبد ويوحد العوالم الثلاثة.
I am about to enter seclusion.
أنا على وشك الدخول في العزلة.
You have nourished me with your clan's rare treasures.
لقد أغذيتني بالكنوز النادرة التي تزخر بها عشيرتك.
You even offered several elders for me to absorb their power.
بل لقد عرضت عليّ عددًا من الشيوخ حتى أتمكن من امتصاص قوتهم.
Today, I will teach you the highest level of Papiyan Devil Art,
اليوم سأعلمك أعلى مستوى من فن شيطان بابيان،
the Star-Devouring Technique.
تقنية التهام النجوم.
Thank you, Cult Leader.
شكرا لك يا زعيم الطائفة.
I will serve you faithfully, even unto death.
سأخدمك بأمانة حتى الموت.
Bring everyone forward.
جلب الجميع إلى الأمام.
Everyone,
الجميع،
you are all clan leaders.
أنتم جميعا زعماء العشائر.
Will you submit to me?
هل ستخضع لي؟
I, Fu Cangtian,
أنا، فو كانغ تيان،
would rather die than be a lackey of the cult.
يفضل الموت على أن يكون تابعًا للطائفة.
Qingyun.
تشينغيون.
Drain him completely.
صفيه بالكامل.
Let me see the beginnings of your Star-Devouring Technique.
دعني أرى بدايات تقنية التهام النجوم الخاصة بك.
What? This...
ماذا؟ هذا...
Qingyun.
تشينغيون.
You are sacrificing your own uncles and brothers.
أنت تضحي بأعمامك وإخوانك.
Could it be
هل يمكن أن يكون
you have no humanity left?
هل لم يبق لك انسانية؟
Qingyun.
تشينغيون.
In this world,
في هذا العالم،
the victors write history.
المنتصرون يكتبون التاريخ.
I believe
انا أؤمن
you should be the Fu family head.
يجب أن تكون رئيس عائلة فو.
Qingyun.
تشينغيون.
I am your father.
انا والدك
Your blood father, bound by blood.
والدك بالدم، مرتبط بالدم.
Silence.
الصمت.
As long as it is for the Cult Leader,
طالما أن الأمر يتعلق بزعيم الطائفة،
nothing is forbidden.
لا يوجد شيء ممنوع.
I thought you would protect me.
اعتقدت أنك سوف تحميني.
But when I was castrated,
ولكن عندما تم خصي،
when my meridians were severed, where were you?
عندما انقطعت خطوط الطول الخاصة بي، أين كنت؟
When you toyed with my woman,
عندما لعبت مع امرأتي،
did you ever consider my feelings?
هل فكرت في مشاعري يوما؟
Though I never truly loved Yan Zhi,
على الرغم من أنني لم أحب يان تشي حقًا،
this proves
هذا يثبت
in your eyes,
في عينيك،
I was never your son,
لم أكن ابنك أبدًا
but a pawn.
بل مجرد بيدق.
The Cult Leader saved me.
لقد أنقذني زعيم الطائفة.
As long as I am loyal to him,
ما دامت أنا مخلصة له،
no one will dare trample me again.
لن يجرؤ أحد على دوسني مرة أخرى.
From now on, the Cult Leader is my true father.
من الآن فصاعدا، زعيم الطائفة هو والدي الحقيقي.
Submit or die.
إستسلم أو مت.
I'd rather die than submit.
أفضّل الموت على الخضوع.
Du Gu Zhantian, you beast!
دو جو زانتيان، أيها الوحش!
I am willing to submit to Demon Sovereign Du Gu Zhantian.
أنا على استعداد للخضوع لسيادة الشيطان دو جو زانتيان.
Worthy of a noble clan leader.
جدير بزعيم عشيرة نبيلة.
You surrendered rather quickly.
لقد استسلمت بسرعة.
Young Master Fu is no different.
السيد الشاب فو ليس مختلفًا.
Utterly loyal to the Demon Sovereign.
مخلص تمامًا لسيادة الشيطان.
Sacrificing family for righteousness.
التضحية بالعائلة من أجل البر.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
Qingyun is the Holy Son of our cult.
تشينغ يون هو الابن المقدس لطائفتنا.
When I am away,
عندما أكون بعيدا،
Fu Qingyun will be the leader of our cult.
فو تشينغ يون سيكون زعيم طائفتنا.
As you command.
كما تأمر.
Thank you, adoptive father.
شكرا لك يا أب بالتبني.
I will obey the Demon Sovereign's orders.
سأطيع أوامر ملك الشيطان.
Cult Leader, what about me?
زعيم الطائفة، ماذا عني؟
I have served you diligently these days.
لقد خدمتك بجد هذه الأيام.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
When I emerge, you will be the Demon Queen.
عندما أخرج، سوف تكونين ملكة الشياطين.
I will now teach you the Star-Devouring Technique.
سأعلمك الآن تقنية التهام النجوم.
Cult Leader.
زعيم الطائفة.
My lord.
سيدي.
I knew only you truly cared for me.
لقد عرفت أنك وحدك من يهتم بي حقًا.
I have finally risen and fulfilled my wish.
لقد نهضت أخيرا وحققت رغبتي.
Congratulations, adoptive father.
ألف مبروك يا أب بالتبني.
Congratulations, adoptive mother.
ألف مبروك يا أم بالتبني.
Report!
تقرير!
Cult Leader!
زعيم الطائفة!
We have located Chen Yuanqi.
لقد حددنا مكان تشين يوانكي.
He is in the Beast God Forest.
هو في غابة إله الوحش.
Qingyun, my child.
تشينغيون، طفلي.
Go with Jiang Shili and kill Chen Yuanqi.
اذهب مع Jiang Shili واقتل Chen Yuanqi.
As you command.
كما تأمر.
My lord.
سيدي.
I want to go too.
أريد أن أذهب أيضاً.
I want to see that jerk die miserably.
أريد أن أرى هذا الأحمق يموت موتًا بائسًا.
Go.
يذهب.
Brother Yuanqi, stop drinking.
الأخ يوانكي، توقف عن الشرب.
Drinking too much will harm your health.
شرب الكثير من الكحول يضر بصحتك.
Can you pull yourself together?
هل تستطيع أن تجمع نفسك معًا؟
Xiao Qiu will always be by your side.
شياو تشيو سيكون دائما بجانبك.
Give it back to me.
أعدها لي.
There's no hope anyway.
لا يوجد أمل على أية حال.
If you don't like it, you can leave.
إذا لم يعجبك ذلك، يمكنك المغادرة.
Brother Yuanqi, please don't make me leave.
الأخ يوانكي، من فضلك لا تجعلني أرحل.
I'll go get you some wine.
سأذهب لأحضر لك بعض النبيذ.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I've studied many ancient texts.
لقد درست العديد من النصوص القديمة.
Only the supreme technique of the Spirit Hound Clan mentions it.
فقط التقنية العليا لعشيرة Spirit Hound هي التي تذكرها.
One can sacrifice their own spirit core.
يمكن للمرء أن يضحي بروحه الأساسية.
There's a fifty percent chance to restore the injured person's meridians.
هناك فرصة تصل إلى خمسين بالمائة لاستعادة خطوط الطول للشخص المصاب.
But only your royal bloodline can use it.
لكن فقط سلالة الدم الملكية الخاصة بك يمكنها استخدامه.
Sacrifice the spirit core.
التضحية بجوهر الروح.
Our Spirit Hound Clan is born and nurtured by nature.
عشيرتنا Spirit Hound ولدت ونشأت بفضل الطبيعة.
The spirit core contains boundless spiritual power.
يحتوي جوهر الروح على قوة روحية لا حدود لها.
But only half have succeeded throughout history.
لكن نصفهم فقط نجحوا عبر التاريخ.
You are the only royal bloodline left in our clan.
أنت السلالة الملكية الوحيدة المتبقية في عشيرتنا.
You must not sacrifice your spirit core for a mere mortal.
لا يجب عليك التضحية بجوهر روحك من أجل مجرد إنسان.
I still want to stay by Brother Yuanqi's side.
لا أزال أرغب في البقاء بجانب الأخ يوانكي.
Don't worry, I won't.
لا تقلق، لن أفعل ذلك.
Lie Shumei.
كذب شومي.
You're back.
لقد عدت.
Am I dreaming?
هل انا احلم؟
Where did you go?
أين ذهبت؟
Why did you leave without saying goodbye?
لماذا رحلت دون وداعا؟
I could have left the Chi You Sword long ago.
كان بإمكاني أن أترك سيف تشي يو منذ زمن طويل.
Why didn't you leave?
لماذا لم تغادر؟
Then why did you come back?
ثم لماذا عدت؟
Did you come to laugh at me?
هل أتيت لتضحك علي؟
To see what you're doing.
لرؤية ما تفعله.
Drinking.
شرب.
Running away.
الهروب.
Where is your courage to defy fate and change destiny?
أين شجاعتك لتحدي القدر وتغيير المصير؟
Defy fate and change destiny.
تحدى القدر وغيّر المصير.
What fate is left for me to defy?
ما هو المصير الذي بقي لي أن أتحدىه؟
What destiny can I change?
ما هو المصير الذي يمكنني تغييره؟
My mother is dead.
لقد ماتت والدتي.
The goddess is dead too.
لقد ماتت الإلهة أيضًا.
Everything is just like before.
كل شيء أصبح كما كان من قبل.
We low-born wretches can never control our fate.
نحن الأشقياء من ذوي الأصول المنخفضة لا يمكننا أبدًا التحكم في مصيرنا.
You dared to face hardship alone.
لقد تجرأت على مواجهة الصعوبات وحدك.
How did you become a coward now?
كيف أصبحت جباناً الآن؟
If you don't even dare to fight Du Gu Zhantian to the end,
إذا لم تجرؤ حتى على قتال دو جو زانتيان حتى النهاية،
how can you be the Chi You Sword Master?
كيف يمكنك أن تصبح سيد سيف تشي يو؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm not worthy.
أنا لا أستحق.
I'm not worthy to be the Chi You Sword Master.
أنا لا أستحق أن أكون سيد سيف تشي يو.
Lie Shumei.
كذب شومي.
You're free anyway.
أنت حر على أية حال.
Why do you still care about me?
لماذا لا تزال تهتم بي؟
Stop caring about me.
توقف عن الاهتمام بي.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
I will abandon the sword and return to the forest.
سأترك السيف وأعود إلى الغابة.
You can leave now.
يمكنك المغادرة الآن.
You're completely free.
أنت حر تماما.
Chen Yuanqi
تشن يوانكي
If you don't come out now
إذا لم تخرج الآن
today will be the day all your beloved women die.
اليوم سيكون اليوم الذي ستموت فيه جميع نسائك الحبيبات.
If you still refuse, I'll kill her.
إذا رفضت مرة أخرى، سأقتلها.
Brother Yuanqi, don't come out! Xiao Qiu!
الأخ يوانكي، لا تخرج! شياو تشيو!
Xiao Qiu
شياو تشيو